Stephanie Chaparro-Roldan

Profile

Florida Atlantic University graduate with a Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration- Marketing. During my time at Florida Atlantic, I was able to complete my 4 year degree in 2 years. I am currently a Premium Support Specialist for Handshake, where I have had the privilege of working directly with thousands of universities and students to further develop their relationships with employers.

Employment History

Premium Support Specialist, Handshake, Remote

2021 - PRESENT

- Works directly with university's career services staff to manage their Handshake account and import thousands of student files
- Updates billion dollar companies' Handshake account branding and directly assists them in troubleshooting issues on a daily basis
- Uses customer relationship management tools (CRM) to constantly track current and potential client interactions
- Builds and analyzes reports using Looker to evaluate individual account data

Field Sales and Marketing Representative, Techtronic Industries , Lake Worth, Florida

AUGUST 2020 - MARCH 2021

- Manages Techronic Industries' products within a \$87 million store
- Analyzes sales and creates marketing strategies in order to further develop the business
- Evaluates the financial aspects of product development, such as budgets, expenditures, research and development appropriations. While taking into account return-on- investment and profit-loss projections
- Identifies marketing strategies, based on knowledge of establishment objectives, market characteristics, and cost factors
- Coordinates marketing activities and policies to promote products and services, while working with advertising and promotion managers.
- Works directly with consumers and corporate officers to establish relationships and further expand the business

Key Holder, Abercrombie & Fitch, Boca Raton, Florida

NOVEMBER 2018 - AUGUST 2020

- Managed a \$3 million store with 40+ employees
- Implemented marketing and updates store merchandise
- Analyzed store profits and losses using key performance indicators
- Developed strategies to increase store conversions and optimize store profits
- Analyzed business trends, customer satisfaction rates, and online sales
- Hired and trained new employees

Education

Bachelor of Business Administration- Marketing, Florida Atlantic University, Boca Raton, Florida

2018 - 2020

Details

Orlando, Florida (407) 243-7485 schaparro2021@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

Skills

Zendesk Proficiency

Salesforce Proficiency

Microsoft Excel

Google Analytics

Trilingual: Spanish, English, and French

JANUARY 2022 - PRESENT

Instructor: Colt Steele

Courses